I feel that all the symbols that I have to read, I have to use only legal language.
Versus it should be like a friendly lawyer who is in your team to help you out.
Language and all this should be understood.
For example, look at this. MCLR, BPLR, these are the things.
So here instead what I want is how the rate is decided.
Usually there are 5 or 6 agencies whose HR is taken.
And then I don't want any advantage or disadvantage from all these agencies.
I want to choose what I should take.
They should tell me that if you don't have much stress, then you go with RBI report.
If you feel that the market is going down in the future,
and the economy is deteriorating, then you take a fixed rate.
If you feel that the economy is going down and the interest rate is going to increase,
then you take a fixed rate.
Then you will get the benefit.
In the same way, I want to know what is the benefit for me,
or when should I choose it as a customer.
I don't want to use the legal language.
And when you take a fixed rate,
even if the fixed rate is 0.25 or higher,
that is also written there.
Yes, that is also written there.
0.25 is higher than the floating rate.
And that is only when the market is going down.
Then you are secured with good rates.
If you feel that the market is going down in India,
then you take a bet.
When our intelligence would suggest that
if India is going down, then you should not take a fixed rate.
floating rate is going to be a favorable term in the long term.
Ok, this is again the same, right?
Yes, it is the same.
Ok, this is also the same, right?
He is the bank.
He is the bank's attribute.
Yes, he is the bank's attribute.
I don't even know the name of the scheme.
Unless a bank has multiple schemes.
There are multiple schemes.
But where are the multiple schemes?
Because the selections are not like that.
When you go up...
Like you had selected top-up, right?
Yes.
These are top-up schemes.
No, it is like this.
I take a home loan.
Or I take a top-up.
I am eligible for two schemes of the same bank.
Is it like that?
Yes, it is like that.
But top-up is only when you don't have a home loan.
No, no.
Either top-up selection or regular selection
means that you can use any bank of the same bank.
You can't use any bank of the same bank in this table.
At any point, only one scheme is applicable.
We don't need to know the name of the scheme.
Not upfront?
No.
At any point,
if there can be multiple schemes applicable,
then we need to know the name of the scheme
so we can decide which scheme to go through via.
Why did you decide that?
Because the customer only has to pay the bank off.
But there is no scheme.
No.
As long as there is only one scheme applicable at one time,
we don't need to know the name of the scheme.
And it won't happen twice.
No, no.
There are two schemes of SBI.
There is a scheme for general public and a special scheme for women.
Have you ever seen such a scheme?
No.
Then a woman will have the right profile
because she will be eligible for both schemes.
Correct?
Yes.
It is like this.
If you are a woman, then you can go through this scheme.
You can also go through this scheme.
If you go through this scheme, you will feel better.
You will feel better.
If you are a woman applicant,
then you can go through this scheme.
If you are a top-up applicant,
Let's go through it now.
In Canada Bank's housing loan,
women are given discounts.
There are no different schemes.
But they have written that
this scheme is only for women.
No, no.
Many banks have schemes like this
that they have different schemes only for women.
Yes.
At that time,
women are also eligible through normal schemes.
And they are also eligible through women schemes.
Then,
what should we do in Himalaya?
That
these schemes,
there are multiple schemes,
but we select the best scheme
and show it.
Then we don't have to tell the name of the scheme.
If a woman is eligible through multiple schemes,
she must be aware
that two schemes should be selected.
PM Yojana
and SCM Yojana.
Both should be selected.
So, I am asking you
that we select the best scheme
Then we don't have to tell the name of the scheme.
Don't select the name of the scheme.
We don't have to add any information.
Yes, we don't have to do that.
So, our compare and apply product.
The comparison product is still there.
We have not taken it yet.
Home page and compare
is done so far.